Karl Moran 29 Old Rectory Park, Taney Road Dundrum, Dublin D14 KT44 karlmorano6@gmail.com

	karlmorano6@gmail.com
20/05/21	
Ref:	
H' a l	
Hi Colm,	

My last role was an Event Executive with Verve the live Agency, since then I had traveled around the world for 2 years after coming home mid pandemic. With this said, I have had the most productive year of my life. I have developed skills in photography and graduated from UCD's Innovation Academy with Diplomas in Creativity, Innovation & Design Thinking and Digital Entrepreneurship & Digital Marketing.

I have a strategic vision and a creative mindset with strong organizational skills that will bring great experience to this role. What I am looking for is a company with a culture of developing talent and recognising employee worth. I am highly motivated and able to work effectively both independently and as part of a team.

An opportunity to work among diverse teams collaborating on innovative events is a dream come true. My attitude towards development and learning is never ending and I hope you see the potential in my application. Creativity and innovation is the way forward.

I would be grateful for a chance to discuss further.

Kind Regards

Karl Moran

Karl Moran -13/06/1993 0872463231

"Goal driven, innovative, and eager to expand my knowledge and skills in events and marketing"

EXPERIENCE

Verve Live Agency, Dublin 2 — Event Executive

February 2017 - January 2018, With my time at Verve I was central to the success of various events. I enjoyed working in a fast paced environment and working with short turn-arounds and deadlines with big branded companies such as Google, Diageo, Ford and many more.

- Sourcing clients for collaborations and events.
- Event planning, organizing and staffing
- On site co-ordination and set up.

Viking Splash Tours, Dublin 8 — Marketing & Sales Intern

November 2016 - February 2017 . This internship allowed me creative freedom to develop and generate marketing strategies. This was a very social position which saw me negotiate contracts and developments with operators and suppliers, along with sourcing various advertising mediums and outlets.

- Management and development of sales e-communication (tripadvisor, dublin tourist.com)
- Website development, advertising and social media management/monitoring.
- Budgeting (advertisement, sales & marketing)

The Westbury Hotel, Dublin 2 – Food & Beverage assistant

July 2011 - September 2016. Employed by the Doyle Collection for over 4 years. As a member of the leading hotels of the world, the Westbury Hotel provided me with invaluable experience in the field of customer service, event planning and business management.

- Maintain standards: LQA.
- Event setup/breakdown.
- Extensive product knowledge

SKILLS

Proficient in Microsoft office, Adobe, Canva, Mural and Wix.

EDUCATION

Institute of Technology, Tallaght, Dublin 24 — BA of business in Marketing Management (2.1 GPA) May 2016

The Photography Institute - Diploma of Professional Photography February 2021

UCD Innovation Academy - UCD Professional Diploma in Transversal Skills - May 2021